Doctor summary (to see all details, run flutter doctor -v):
[ΓêÜ] Flutter (Channel stable, 3.41.4, on Microsoft Windows [Version 10.0.26200.8037], locale en-ID)
[ΓêÜ] Windows Version (11 Home Single Language 64-bit, 25H2, 2009)
[X] Android toolchain - develop for Android devices
    X Unable to locate Android SDK.
      Install Android Studio from: https://developer.android.com/studio/index.html
      On first launch it will assist you in installing the Android SDK components.
      (or visit https://flutter.dev/to/windows-android-setup for detailed instructions).
      If the Android SDK has been installed to a custom location, please use
      `flutter config --android-sdk` to update to that location.

[ΓêÜ] Chrome - develop for the web
[!] Visual Studio - develop Windows apps (Visual Studio Community 2022 17.14.13 (August 2025))
    X Visual Studio is missing necessary components. Please re-run the Visual Studio installer for the "Desktop development with C++" workload, and include these components:
        MSVC v142 - VS 2019 C++ x64/x86 build tools
         - If there are multiple build tool versions available, install the latest
        C++ CMake tools for Windows
        Windows 10 SDK
[ΓêÜ] Connected device (3 available)
[ΓêÜ] Network resources

! Doctor found issues in 2 categories.
